Timothy LaRoy Jr.

8236 Dodd Cir Fort Meade, MD 20755 timlaroy93@gmail.com (703) 909 - 5511 Github: https://github.com/KrombopulOs Portfolio: https://krombopulOs.github.io/portfolio

ABOUT

Marine veteran with a passion for helping others and learning about the world of technology. A proven leader with experience training and taking responsibility for individuals and large groups. Possesses the drive and resourcefulness to find solutions and go beyond to ensure overwhelming success individually and in teams.

FORMAL EDUCATION

Concordia University - Chicago - M.S. Applied Exercise Science - Strength & Conditioning Concentration

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

American Military University - B.S. Sports & Health Science Jan 2018 - Dec 2019

CERTIFICATIONS, COURSEWORK, and SKILLS LEARNED

- COMPTIA A+
- Google Data Analytics Specialization Coursera
 - o R, SQL, Excel, Data Handling
- Google IT Support Specialization Coursera
 - IT support industry standards relating to windows and linux
- **JavaScript Specialization** Duke University
- Python Programming Specialization University of Michigan

WORK HISTORY

MCCS Quantico - Russell Knox Fitness Center - Fitness Specialist

Mar 2021 - May 2021 POC: Kim Ryan (571) 305-4581

Programmed and executed individual and group fitness training.

Online Strength Coach (self employed)

Jun 2018 - Jan 2021

- Directly oversaw the training of multiple types of athletes and clients
- Identified and corrected movement dysfunctions resolving acute pain

USMC - Search and Rescue/Maintenance Control Chief
Oct 2012 - Oct 2017 POC: N/A (unit shut down)

- Responsible for 40+ Marines, 4 aircraft, and a multi-million dollar account
- Organized daily operations for squadron and oversaw the training of the unit leading to highest squadron readiness in all of Marine Corps